<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="12"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[May 29,1953









                                         Written and illustrated by :

                                                 Sarra Ben Amara




































                                             English Board Collection]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[Today is the most important day of my life. I finally


      climbed Mt. Everest, the tallest mountain in the


      world.]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[The top of the mountain was amazing. It felt like we



      were close to heaven. The snow was so thick that my


      boots sank. The air was silent. I looked at the beauty


      that surrounded me. Maybe my story will be a legend


      someday.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[I want people to remember this forever. I was the


      senior explorer in my group, and I knew we needed


      proof of our climb. I took many pictures with my


      camera. I’ll put them in a frame and hang them.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[On the mountain, the air was very cold. I wrapped


       my coat around my body.I looked over the side of


       the mountaintop. From that angle, I saw the border


       of the clouds touch the rocks below.]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[The snow was thick. It looked pure. There was


       no sign of modern life. Thousands of years ago, my


       ancestors saw the world this way.]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[After fifteen minutes, I knew it was time to proceed


     down the mountain. The whole team congratulated us.


     My superior, John Hunt, praised us all.]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[I sent messages to my relatives to tell them that I


        was safe. But it was hard to leave the mountain so


        quickly. I wanted to enjoy the incredible sight even


        longer.]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[Check your understanding


































                                             English Board Collection]]></page></pages></Search>